ecobank.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy

| 

Privacy Policy   
  
---|---  
  
## Our Privacy Pledge 

Your identity is one of the most valuable assets. Learn more about what you can do to protect your identity, and what Ecobank is doing to protect it for you.

## Ecobank Privacy Policy

## Our Philosophy Regarding Your Personal Financial Information 

At Ecobank, we have a long history of respecting our customers’ expectation of privacy regarding personal financial information. We value the trust you place in us to protect your personal information. While new technologies have dramatically changed the way information is gathered, used and stored, preserving customer trust and the confidentiality of personal information at Ecobank remains a core objective. 

We believe it is important to make clear to our customers how information is being used at Ecobank, the benefits such use provides, and the protections put in place against unauthorized access and use. We respect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information, and we appreciate the opportunity to do business with you. 

## What We Collect 

The non-public personal customer information we collect includes information we receive from applications or other loan and account forms submitted to the Bank and its subsidiaries. 

## How We Use This Information for Everyday Business Purposes 

To run our everyday business, we share customer information with service-providers who assist us in servicing customer accounts and preparing and/or delivering bank services and products to our customers. Examples of such providers include check printers, check verification services, mortgage payment facilitators and credit reporting agencies. 

## Why And What We Share With Affiliates 

We share customer information concerning your transactions and experience within the Ecobank Group (the bank), which includes our mortgage and securities affiliates. A list of the bank’s family of companies is located in page ”our network” . This sharing of information is intended only to facilitate the servicing of our customers’ accounts and to offer financial products and services we believe would be beneficial to our customers.

## Why And What We Share With Joint Marketing Partners 

We also share limited customer information with our joint marketing partners, which include insurance companies, allowing us to offer a variety of financial products and services we endorse and believe you may find beneficial. The information we share is limited to information provided on applications. Under all sharing arrangements, the bank requires its service providers and marketing partners to keep such information confidential and prohibits them from disclosing such information to anyone for any other purpose. 

We obtain only limited medical information required to initiate a customer’s request for insurance products or services. In those instances, we will forward that information to the insurance company only to facilitate obtaining the insurance product for which you apply. We will not otherwise disclose such information to anyone unless authorized by the customer or required by law, and we will not use this information for any other purpose. 

We do not, and will not, share customer information with non-financial companies for the purpose of allowing them to market their products and services to our customers. 

We do not disclose any non-public personal information about our customers to any other third parties, except as permitted or required by law. 

## How We Protect Your Information

We have developed strong security measures to protect customer privacy. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your non-public personal information.

If you decide to close your account(s) or your account(s) become inactive, we will continue to adhere, as required by law, to the Bank’s current privacy policies and practices. 

## How to Limit Information Sharing

If you wish to limit our sharing of your personal information with our joint marketing partners or our affiliates, please contact us at our contact center numbers **(Kindly visit our "CONTACT US" section in this website)**. You will still receive periodic statement inserts or other offers in our regular mailings to you. 

If you have requested to be removed from marketing communications/lists, it is your responsibility to alert Ecobank of a subsequent change of address, because the address is a necessary component for identifying customers who choose not to receive marketing communications.

**The Ecobank Group**   
Ecobank Transnational Incorporated  
2365, Boulevard du Mono  
BP 3261  
Lomé (Togo)  
Phone: (228) 22 21 03 03 / 22 21 31 68  
Fax: (228) 22 21 51 19
